(We Have Become a Family)
They'll see what real running is all about now.
Gosh, it is different.
He's starting on an uphill to make our run look like nothing.
Right.
It's so annoying.
(He heads somewhere after a proper run.)
Gosh, I'm tired.
(Ringing)
Where is this place?
(Barking)
- Food. - Hey.
- Your brother is back from his run. - Come here. Hey.
Your brother came back from his exercise.
Come here.
- My goodness. - Come here.
- Oh, my. They're so cute! - Come back here.
- It's your brother. - They're Alkong and Dalkong.
Come here.
It's your brother.
Dalkong.
I came to visit my mother on Jeju Island...
- after a long time. - Alkong.
- Come here. - After our dog, Candy,
passed away,
the house felt very empty.
We brought them home around last winter.
(Alkong easily fell asleep in his mother's arms.)
Alkong.
- That's Alkong. - He's sticking out his tongue.
(Pushing it out)
(Dalkong stayed glued to Kian84.)
- Dalkong. - This is Dalkong.
- Alkong and Dalkong. - The timid one.
Alkong is used to being around people.
- He can get along with people. - Are you happy?
He's a friendly dog.
(He quickly adjusted to his new environment.)
But Dalkong...
- came from a puppy mill. Naturally, - I see.
- That's not good. - he's very shy.
- Right. - When we first brought him home,
he didn't bark.
- My goodness, he was scared. - He always felt intimidated.
- He's shaking. It's okay. - Really?
(After the fostering period ended last winter, they moved to Jeju.)
They're living in a great place.
Seriously. They can go to the beach every day. This is so nice.
(They began their lives in Jeju known for clean water.)
Alkong. Dalkong.
They're so cute.
Both humans and dogs need to be loved.
- Of course. - That's right.
I can tell your mother gave them a lot of love.
Now that they're staying with my mother,
they seemed more energetic than when we first met.
They must feel confident now. They started to bark.
- That's right. My goodness. - They're different now.
Dalkong looks so energetic now.
We have an old picture of him in a cage.
- It will make you cry. Seriously. - Let's eat.
- Let's go inside and eat. - Right.
Let's go inside and eat.
- Let's go inside and eat. - Go in.
- Dalkong. - Jeju Island had only...
- uphills. It was so exhausting. - Let's go in and eat. Hurry.
- Hey. - Gosh, he feels comfortable there.
(He plops down on the sofa as soon as he comes in.)
She moved into this house 4 or 5 years ago.
(Kian84's face is seen all over her house.)
(A portrait of Kian84 personally drawn by his mother)
Your mother... That's crazy.
She started drawing for fun...
- when she moved to Jeju Island. No. - But she never studied?
She never took classes. It's her hobby.
The artistic talent must run in the family.
- Definitely. - You got the talent from her.
It does run in the family.
(Hyun Moo's painting is on display too.)
- Wait. - That's Kian84.
You're good at art, Hyun Moo.
- Seriously. Your art has that vibe. - Why do you like my art so much?
It looks great. I mean it.
You didn't throw it out.
I was wondering where it went. It turned out she had it.
Are you serious? You didn't know where it had gone?
- What was that supposed to be? - Come on.
- What? - The letters on the painting.
- Why did I write them? - It's completely different.
- "Why?" - Did you forget?
- Why did I write them? - "Fashion King." "Returning King."
- The titles of my webtoons. - "Fashion King."
How could you forget about your own art?
Art is up to the interpretation of the recipient.
- It's up to their interpretation. - That's right. I remember it now.
Oh, right.
(It's also full of cute ornaments.)
I love your mom's house.
I wonder why moms love owls.
I know, right? My mom has them too.
I sometimes use this room when I come over.
But it's a guestroom, so it's a bit chilly inside.
That's why it's not so comfortable to sleep in here.
My house is much more comfortable.
It's time for your meal now.
Let's eat.
You guys are going to eat.
And your brother is going to eat too.
"Brother."
- Be quiet. - How many months has it been?
How long?
I brought them home on December 11.
- They moved here in December? - Yes.
It's already been four months?
- It's been over four months. - Let me feed them.
- Go inside the house for food. - They don't know what it is.
- What? - To the house!
(He confidently tries to feed them.)
- Come on. To the house. - Alkong...
Dalkong, to the house.
They did a great grooming job. His legs are beautifully trimmed.
That's what you're noticing now.
- Dalkong, to the house. - Dalkong, to the house.
Feed Alkong first.
- Then Dalkong will figure it out. - Right.
We're training them to go inside the kennel...
- and eat their food there. - Dalkong, to the house.
- Dalkong, to the house. - Go in if you want your food.
- He can be scary. - To the house.
I hadn't seen them in a while, so they didn't recognize me.
- Really? - They were shy around me.
Give it to him.
He can be scary. Come here.
Dalkong. Eat comfortably here.
- Come here, Dalkong. - Why do they have to eat in there?
- People train them to eat in there. - Kennel training is nice.
- Why? - That way, they don't fight.
- I see. So they won't fight. - Dogs can fight.
- You go and wash up quickly. - Okay.
I'll eat after I wash up.
Hee Min, to the house.
(Hee Min, to the house!)
If you want food, go into the house.
Hee Min, to the house.
(Pulling out)
I guess it's a rule that moms must have plates like that.
- The national plate. - Right.
The national plate.
(As she thinks about her son who will enjoy her food,)
(a hearty meal is coming together.)
Food cooked by moms.
That's the best.
(Meanwhile, he's done with his shower.)
(Feeling refreshed)
- Hee Min, come on down. - Okay.
(Grunting)
See? You get so tired...
- after a proper run. - Right.
- I was so tired. - He's so fatigued.
(He drags his tired body down for breakfast.)
You want to come to me?
Your brother is here. Let's give him his food.
Your brother should eat now.
Your brother should eat now. Hurry.
Be quiet.
Hey, he's smelling you.
- Be quiet. - Give them...
- What? - Give them...
- Be quiet. - Give them your hand.
- What? - Give them your hand.
He's smelling you. There you go.
- You don't remember him? - You must be a stranger to them.
- They treated me like a stranger. - Right?
Gosh, they're so loud.
(The brothers need to get used to being around each other.)
Come here.
I was really craving some breakfast after a proper run.
This is sea urchin roe.
Wrap up some rice with the dried laver.
- This is Jeju Island. - Jeju is in a different league.
- This is a red tilefish. Eat it up. - Okay.
The red tilefish was great with rice.
This is Korean beef.
She cooked Korean beef too.
You're not going to eat?
- Gosh, that looks so good. - I don't have an appetite.
Oh, my. It looks great.
(An epic spread of food)
- Try the sea urchin roe first. - Okay.
- Have the beef too. - The sea urchin roe?
What? Try them together.
My gosh. Look at that beautiful color.
- When I brought them from Seoul... - Yes.
Gosh, I'm getting hungry.
- It was really good. - This is good.
- Jeju is famous for red tilefish. - Jeju Island...
It tastes so good.
She deboned the fish for him.
By the way, he's gotten more comfortable around people.
Oh, definitely.
Dalkong has improved so much. Isn't that right?
I was worried at first.
But he loves his teacher. He's a guy too.
That's good, Mom. I'll do it myself.
- He's a guy too. - That's good, Mom.
I'll do it myself.
No. Have some of this too.
You keep telling me to eat.
But still. You must eat more.
They remind me of my mom and me.
That's how it is for moms and sons.
I was already eating, but she kept giving me more food.
When you're trying to chew down the fish, she gives you tangerines.
Right.
(He takes a big bite, feeling self-conscious around her.)
They're not barking at each other.
- Right. They play with each other. - They're having fun together.
Hyun Moo also adopted a dog.
Right. Just yesterday, I texted the director of the shelter...
where we brought Alkong and Dalkong.
The director told me that Hyun Moo's mom adopted one too.
Well, my parents feel lonely.
Going to the hospital is the only thing they do.
The chances of my getting married and giving them a grandchild...
are pretty slim.
So I thought giving them a new family member was better.
I wanted to adopt one from a shelter and had been looking for one.
That's when Kian84 and his mother adopted a dog.
I asked him to introduce me to the director.
We adopted a dog three days ago from the same shelter.
- Really? - That was pretty recent.
My parents are with the dog.
- You have a new family member. - That's right.
They're so happy now.
We kept thinking about it. And we decided on this one.
Adopting a dog from a shelter and running.
Strangely, they keep doing the same thing.
(A mysterious theory of the parallel universe)
Ito Junji remains now.
(Oh, no. Don't take him away from me.)
I'm so busy in the morning because of them.
They go to kindergarten three days a week.
- Three days a week. - They go to kindergarten too?
Dogs go to kindergarten?
Apparently, they do.
They go to kindergarten three days a week.
- I drop them off and pick them up. - Seriously.
(Grabbing)
Gosh, they have a backpack.
So cute.
I need to pack their food.
What kind of world are we living in now?
(Confused)
I need to pack their lunch.
My gosh. She's packing their lunch.
- I wonder where it had gone wrong. - No.
You can't think that sending them there is wrong.
They can go there and get trained.
That way, they can enjoy their lives too.
That's common these days.
(He's on the same page.)
- Okay. - Peekaboo.
Let me pack your lunch.
It's time for kindergarten.
(Leaving her indifferent son behind...)
She's packing their food.
(She's packing their favorite dog food for lunch.)
Dalkong. Alkong. Let's go to kindergarten.
- Look at his backpack. - So cute.
My goodness. He's gotten much more cheerful now.
He won't even look at them.
(I should just eat my food.)
Let's go to kindergarten.
(Reaching up)
Gosh, he's such a cutie.
They brighten up my mother's morning a lot.
- She now... - Right.
- That's right. - has a routine.
- You're excited, Alkong. - You have a lovely mother.
I see.
- Do you want more rice? - No.
- Yes? Why don't you... - I just want the tofu.
You should eat a lot.
(He goes after doenjang jjigae instead of getting more rice.)
(Slurping)
This is good.
It's nice to see you enjoying the food.
Moms love that the most.
- Let me give you rice. It's salty. - No.
(He keeps on slurping the stew without any rice.)
Oh, my. You barely touched that expensive sea urchin roe.
- Right. - Gosh, he didn't finish that?
Why is your doenjang jjigae so good?
- What? - Gosh.
- Well, I'm... - This is your best doenjang jjigae.
- It's the best doenjang jjigae? - Yes.
- This is just crazy. - That's so sweet.
- Really? - Yes.
Did he really say that?
Forget about ramyeon or gukbap.
I don't need anything. This is the best.
We both like food grannies like.
No. Your doenjang jjigae is amazing.
So you like it.
- Thank you for the food. - Okay.
Oh, no. I must hurry and drop them off at kindergarten.
- Let's go to kindergarten, Dalkong. - They're late.
It's time for kindergarten, Dalkong.
When I mention kindergarten,
- he comes for his leash. - He likes going there.
- He loves going there. - Let's go to kindergarten, Dalkong.
You're excited to see your brother.
(They quickly get ready to go to kindergarten.)
My goodness. They're so young.
Take their backpacks.
Put them on your shoulder.
(Looking sour)
- He doesn't like that. - Let's go.
When dog kindergartens sprang up,
it made me wonder...
we were living in a transition period.
- That's deep. - That crossed my mind.
But on one hand,
there must be a demand...
for a service like this to exist.
(A sharp inhale)
It's quite puzzling.
It is.
I understand what you mean.
When I first heard about dog kindergartens,
it made me wonder for whose benefit they existed.
- That was my first question. - You were objective.
But they offered necessary training services.
They can develop social skills. It's great.
We can only spend limited time to play with them.
- We feel bad. - That's right.
- They can also go for walks. - We're busy.
- Right. - They can go for walks...
- and develop social skills. - That's right.
We send them to kindergarten, so they can play with their friends.
Dogs also get depressed...
- when they only stay home. - Exactly.
Let's go to kindergarten.
- They leave quite early. - Let's go to kindergarten.
- I'm curious what they do there. - Right here.
- Let's go. - All right.
Let's go and turn you into the smartest dog.
- Go to your brother. - Come here.
- Let's go. - Gosh, they're so cute.
Let's go to kindergarten.
- This is sort of like "SKY Castle." - Right.
(They head out to the dog kindergarten.)
Actually,
I talked to the director of their shelter yesterday.
- We text from time to time. - Okay.
I heard all the dogs we met there got adopted.
- Right. They were all adopted. - That's great news.
- They all got adopted. - You helped them get adopted.
- That's great news. - Right.
- You took pictures of them. - Right.
- Seriously. - They haven't found a home yet.
- I just can't stop looking at them. - Oh, no.
(He couldn't stop thinking about...)
(the dogs who didn't get adopted.)
- That's so important. - They got adopted, though.
You're amazing.
(They all found a new home and got adopted.)
- They all went to nice families. - Yes.
- What a relief. - I kept thinking about them.
- So we were just chatting. - Okay.
I told her that Dalkong became the president.
(I told her that Dalkong became the president.)
- What? - There's a president too?
- I... - The president?
- How do they pick the president? - You're not happy with it.
- My gosh, the president? - They held an election for it.
- Really? - They did.
The number of likes on social media counted as votes.
- The dog owners also voted. - I see.
The dogs somehow voted too.
- That's a democratic way to do it. - Right.
- I guess they go to the candidate. - Like that?
I guess that's how they vote.
(Laughing)
They also have sports days and so on.
- Sports days? - They do.
- They have sports days. - They play dodgeball together.
They have events for Puppy Day,
- That's cute. - Parents' Day,
- and so on. - Oh, that's so cute.
They're doing things her grandchildren should do...
because I failed to give her one.
We're in the same boat.
I couldn't give them grandchildren.
I adopted a dog for them.
I should keep an open mind today.
Yes. You should be open to many possibilities.
Okay. Yes, sir.
Today's episode is fun.
(Intrigued)
(The brother hears the news about Dalkong's presidency.)
- I... - The president?
This time around, there were six candidates.
You mean, six dogs. They're not real people.
They're like my own children.
I don't see them as mere dogs.
- I'm proud of Dalkong. - My gosh, it was like a festival.
So...
- Should I be happy about this? - What?
Does he have any power as the president?
- Who knows? - Since he's the president,
ask the kindergarten to give us a discount.
What?
Ask them for a discount or something.
- Anyway, I thought it was so funny. - Okay.
I decided to give out rice cakes...
- She looks so happy. - to celebrate his presidency.
- She'll give out rice cakes? - I really should.
This is a great occasion for rice cakes.
I'm not sure about this.
But the problem is Dalkong doesn't know he's the president.
- He knows. - Exactly.
He'd never know.
He must know. I'm sure he's proud of himself.
So my friends and I texted a lot...
about the election.
They wrote things like, "Dalkong for President."
We had so much fun with the election.
(Confused)
I bet there are so many things he wants to say.
A while ago, she started...
texting me.
She asked me to write a comment and vote on some platform.
I asked her about it.
She told me that Dalkong was running for president.
I asked her not to do stuff like that.
Why not?
There were campaign pledges. They were even more annoying.
- What were the campaign pledges? - The campaign pledges were...
"I will share my snacks..."
"with my friends."
That's so cute!
Dalkong.
- That's so adorable. - "I'll make..."
- Oh, my goodness. - "a happy environment for dogs."
That's so cute.
Seriously. I don't even know...
how I'm supposed to feel about that.
I saw these crazy promises on the campaign poster.
- He's not exactly wrong. - It's...
- It's true. They do sound crazy. - Right. He's not wrong.
- Right. - But my mother...
- and other dog owners... - Right.
were having so much fun with it.
- So I thought it was meaningful. - Right.
That's what I thought.
- And dogs look happy too. - Right.
- That's true too. - Right.
I'm glad that...
- they make my mom happy. - Right.
Seriously.
By the way, I signed Dalkong up...
for the election for a reason.
- Alkong... - For his social skills?
doesn't need me.
- Right. - But my heart breaks for Dalkong.
He's still shy and nervous around people.
I signed Dalkong up for the election,
so his teacher would pay more attention to him.
That was the reason behind my decision.
And his teacher told me that...
Dalkong improved a lot over these few months.
- I can see his improvement too. - Okay.
Do you know what he does when I drop him off?
He'd look at me with these sad eyes.
- Then he'd follow his teacher. Yes. - He'd still go?
He needs to improve his social skills.
I went to kindergarten too. How come I don't have social skills?
(I went to kindergarten too. How come I don't have social skills?)
Gosh, it's only kindergarten.
Gosh, people don't turn out the same even if they go to kindergarten.
- Right. - Everyone is different.
Look at Alkong and Dalkong.
- They're completely different. - Right.
It's the same with people. It depends on the personality.
- Right. - You know? Everyone knows that.
But it's more touching that the introverted one, Dalkong,
became the president.
I heard there were special districts for dog schools these days.
Gosh, some people send their dogs to English kindergarten.
- What? - English kindergarten for dogs?
How could they go to English kindergarten?
(Shocked)
That's what I heard.
(The news of the new world makes him laugh in disbelief.)
That's crazy.
Oh, I think I know what it is.
Some people train their dogs in English like, "Sit."
- "Sit." - "Sit."
- "Wait." - "Stand."
- Some dogs get adopted abroad. - No. That's...
- Right. - That makes sense then.
The thing is, I keep finding both sides understandable.
So I'm caught in the middle.
I never went to kindergarten.
My nose is tickling.
We're here.
Become amazing dogs.
My gosh, it's up.
Goodness, Dalkong is up there.
Oh, my.
(His picture is on the banner at the entrance.)
- My gosh. - Okay.
- Congratulations. - Gosh.
(The president of Class Good Manners is here.)
You've won.
I see. Each class has a president.
- The photos of presidents are up. - "The president."
- "The vice-president." - "The vice-president."
Chui is the vice-president.
This is just like Daechi-dong.
Alkong. Dalkong.
- Dalkong. - That's good. Open the door.
Their backpacks. Hold on.
- He's annoyed. - Gosh, Dalkong.
(He spots something and walks over.)
This is crazy.
(Campaign posters are hanging at the gate.)
- What? "Park Boknam?" - Participation is all that matters.
"He won the battle with Park Boknam."
(Among the pocket-sized candidates...)
- They all had campaign pledges. - Of course.
(The gallant Dalkong threw his hat into the ring.)
So cute.
Dalkong looks so gallant.
(And...)
Oh, my. Look at Dalkong.
(he was elected president.)
That's something else.
(The congratulatory banners are everywhere.)
Seriously. Unbelievable.
(He brought glory to his family.)
Look at his eyes.
Look at his charisma.
"I'll take care of my class."
- Look at him. He looks so reliable. - Over here.
(Adoring)
- Which big dog ended up winning? - Among...
This one. Sunny became the president.
Sunny won?
Sunny looks like the president.
I heard that this one lost the election four years in a row.
Hodu lost four years in a row?
- This was his fourth election? - This time around...
- He tried out for the 4th time? - Was it his 5th try?
- Yes. It was his fourth try. - Oh, no. Hodu.
- Hodu, change the campaign pledges. - Hodu.
Poor Hodu.
I wonder if he'll try again.
Will Hodu run for the fifth time?
What? Hodu became the president this time.
Hodu became the president?
(Hodu finally became the president.)
- Hello. - Teacher.
- Hello. - Hello.
Alkong and Dalkong.
- How cute. - Hello.
- Please put Dalkong down. - Okay.
Please put Alkong and Dalkong down.
- My goodness. - They're excited.
- Hee Min. - Yes?
- She is the assistant director... - Okay.
and he is the homeroom teacher.
- The homeroom teacher? - So there is a homeroom teacher.
They adore the dogs.
(They adore Alkong and Dalkong.)
- Thank you. - We'll go inside...
- after walking around the yard. - Okay.
- Let's go, Alkong and Dalkong. - Let's go.
Alkong and Dalkong, let's go.
(Staring)
- Does being the president have... - Let's go.
- any perks? - There should be perks.
One perk is the letter of appointment.
- The letter of appointment. - Also, as you can see,
- the elected ones get celebrated. - Right.
(I see.)
I'll bring some rice cake next week.
- Dalkong became the president. - So I should bring some rice cake.
- Dalkong became the president. - The winner usually buys pizza.
- That's right. - All right.
(All right.)
They dote on their mom.
They dote on their mom. They only follow their mom.
- Seriously. - Teacher.
Let's make a round...
before going into the classroom.
All right.
Dalkong dotes on his mom.
Don't look at me when you run. Look ahead when you run.
Don't look at me.
- For midterms, - Okay.
they practice how to walk alongside people.
- He is walking well. - Is he walking well?
- Yes. He is doing an amazing job. - Midterms.
Soon, they'll take exams.
- What exams? - Midterms are in May.
They'll get tested on walking well by their parents' side.
He is doing a good job now.
Dalkong is doing a good job now.
Is it like a three-legged race? Is it like a field day?
We have midterms. We have two midterms a year.
(Midterms, not a field day)
We have two midterms a year.
During midterms, they get tested on commands such as "Sit" and "Wait..."
or their ability to walk alongside people.
They can't cram for such exams.
- Of course not. - No.
- They need to do it regularly. - They need to practice daily.
Yes. They need to do it regularly.
We'll score their performances and give them grades.
- Grades. - Yes.
(We'll give them grades for the midterms.)
I felt like...
I was in a strange dream.
I felt like those dogs were my children...
and my mom's grandchildren.
- It's like webcomics. - Right.
This is driving me crazy.
I hope they place first.
If they place first, they'll receive an excellence award.
Awards will pile up at home.
(Feeling dizzy)
- Please take good care of them. - Okay.
- See you later, Mr. Kim. - You seem like the dad.
- See you later. - Okay.
Thank you.
Visit them on Teachers' Day, okay?
(Visit them on Teachers' Day, okay?)
(After dropping the dogs off, they head somewhere.)
The kindergarten is so funny.
They have exams and midterms. That's so funny.
In May, they'll also have a Children's Day event.
Moms find that fun.
- They know it's ridiculous. - Such things...
- entertain her. - That's right. It's happiness.
Will it rain? What's up with the weather?
They said the sky would clear up in the afternoon.
It won't rain.
I think we're here.
Is this the place? It's here. It isn't big, is it?
- It's small. - Yes.
- Let's park here, Mom. - Okay.
Did she buy a plot of land?
She didn't buy a plot of land.
When the dogs moved from the mainland to the island,
one person could board the plane with one dog.
Since my mom couldn't take both of them,
her friend traveled all the way to Seoul to help her...
and boarded the plane with the other dog.
(Her friend accompanied her to Seoul and brought Alkong and Dalkong.)
- They brought the dogs that way. - I'm so thankful.
My mom was indebted to her,
so she asked me to help with some farm work.
I went there because there was a lot of work.
I don't know which variety it is.
- I think they're here. - Yes.
- Jeong Hye. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Auntie who brought Alkong... - Hello.
- and her husband. - Thank you.
You can give me any kind of work.
- That's right. - Will you be able to do it?
- You look quite strong. - Give him a lot of work.
Since you help me all the time,
he can work for a day.
(Nodding)
The stone wall...
- needs to be repaired. - I see the damage.
We need to repair the stone wall and cut down the bamboo.
I can use my muscles.
- Make him use his muscles. - I like that.
Make him work like a servant.
(Servant DNA stirs at the thought of working.)
Servant DNA.
Hee Min is an incredible worker.
Servant84.
Mom, go and have a cup of coffee.
Okay.
- I can't work because of my back. - How cool!
- Jeong Hye! - Yes?
Go ahead and work with Hee Min.
I'll get going.
Okay, President's Mom.
(Okay, President's Mom.)
He doesn't like that.
(The president's mom takes a break.)
(This servant gets left behind.)
- This is the stone wall. - Was it very windy?
How did it collapse?
When the workers were cutting down the coastal hogfennel,
- the stone wall collapsed. - It happened during work.
- Yes, it happened during work. - It can withstand wind.
- Place rock like this. - Okay.
If you keep circling it,
- it'll stop moving at a point. - Okay.
- That's how you know it's in place. - I see.
It's even now, right?
- Okay. - Here.
(They begin to build the stone wall.)
My goodness. It's hard work.
I know.
(Heave-ho)
You pile up rocks like that.
Basalt rocks are perfect for piling up.
- They're light. - Yes.
They're bumpy too.
What's fascinating is that a well-built wall doesn't collapse.
- Really? - The rocks aren't glued.
The rocks fit together like puzzle pieces.
It's like "Tetris."
(Oh, my!)
- What is it? - Look at this worm.
Thanks to the quality soil,
- the worms get big. - Look at this worm.
- How is it so big? - What?
- Is that a snake? - It's so big.
It's big.
(Staring)
Will you run to become the president?
(By any chance, will you run to become the president?)
Let's become the president.
The worm should go to the kindergarten.
The kindergarten.
The worm has midterms next week.
They'll get tested on digging into the soil fast.
They have midterms next week, so that worm is practicing.
Digging into the soil!
Go back.
(Go back and study for the exams.)
Seriously.
(Putting down)
(Looking for rocks to pile up)
- Oh, my! - Is there another one?
It's a pill bug.
A cute pill bug.
Thanks to the quality soil, you can find all sorts of things.
Do you go to the kindergarten too?
Are you the president too?
- They learn how to roll up fast. - How to roll up.
(Go and study for the exams.)
(After keeping a bug from studying, he gets back to work.)
(Piling up rocks)
(Piling up more rocks)
(Lifting)
(Servant84 can even lift up a boulder.)
- It's a big one. - Be careful.
Okay.
(Heave-ho)
- Moving rocks suits you. - Yes.
(Servant84 becomes absorbed in moving rocks.)
- He is good. - Yes.
Piling up rocks for the stone wall was fun.
It was like assembling the building blocks.
The pieces come together when you don't expect them to.
The pieces come together perfectly.
I think that's pretty fun.
(To be continued)
- Between the rocks... - What's this?
My heart is fluttering.
(Servant84 is working hard to restore the stone wall.)
- Between the rocks... - What's this?
Like this, fill up the space between the rocks.
- My heart is fluttering. - It's like a music video.
So that they fit...
(He fills up the empty spots with his diligence.)
- There. - It's the shot of your first love.
(Boyfriend at the library)
He looks the same.
(Boyfriend at the tangerine field)
- First love. - It's like an ad of Jeju water.
(It's like a commercial.)
Kian84.
(The senior we loved back then, Hee Min)
There.
It's cool.
(He stays cool until the end when he restores the stone wall.)
There.
Now, the stone wall won't collapse no matter what.
- Okay. - Follow me.
- Let's go to the auntie's side. - There is so much work.
- There are rocks, right? - Yes.
Pick up the rocks.
(Pick up the rocks on the ground and put them on the side.)
- Pile up the rocks on the side. - Okay.
Shall I pile them up?
We need to move the rocks we've collected.
- Okay. - In Jeju dialect, it's "Eoyeom."
- "Eoyeom?" - Yes.
- "Eoyeom?" - What's that?
It means "Side."
- Side. - Yes.
- "Eoyeop?" - Eoyeom.
- Eoyeom. - Eoyeom.
- Side. - Yes. Side.
("Eoyeom" means "Side," right?)
Are you from Jeju Island?
- I'm a native. - Are you a native?
I see.
You won't understand me if I use the Jeju dialect.
Would you say something?
(He becomes curious.)
Gosh, you sokakjeoing to come here.
"You sokakjeoing to come here."
"You must've gotten fooled to come here."
Does it mean something else?
It means that you've struggled.
- Is that the meaning? - Yes.
(It means that he has struggled.)
"When Life Gives You Tangerines..."
- has taught us that. - Yes.
Do you know what this is called in Jeju dialect?
What?
What is this called in Jeju dialect?
Sickle?
- Homi. - "Homi?"
- What? - Really?
What we call "Homi" is a triangular tool.
That's gwolgaengi.
- "Gwolgaengi?" - Gwolgaengi.
- What's that called? - Homi.
People call it "Homi" in Seoul too.
We call it a sickle.
- Really? - No, we call it a sickle.
- Sickle. - Homi.
- Is a sickle called "Homi?" - Yes.
(He finally understands.)
It's different.
What you call "Homi" in Seoul is called "Gwolgaengi" here.
Here, this is "Homi."
- Is that "Homi?" - Yes.
It's different.
Brother, give me the sickle!
(Brother, give me the sickle!)
(You said that a sickle was called "Homi" on Jeju Island.)
What?
It's so funny to see him walk away without a word.
He asked for the sickle, and he understood that.
(He is funny.)
(Let's hurry up and move the rocks.)
Fields on Jeju Island are...
- half soil and half rocks. - Right.
It'll take me forever to move the rocks.
(Grunting)
Gosh, these rocks.
Gosh, look at all these rocks.
(Meanwhile, his fur siblings are receiving education.)
Alkong.
Let's go.
A person does manual labor...
while dogs receive education.
(He spreads fertilizer.)
(The eldest son, Hee Min, works diligently for his mom.)
(Feeling sad)
- Hee Min. - Yes?
It's time to take Alkong and Dalkong home.
- Is it time to pick them up? - Yes, it's time to pick them up.
You can stop working now.
- Shall I stop? - Yes. We need to pick them up.
- You need to pick them up. - Really?
Thank you for your hard work today.
I was going to work until sunset.
Until sunset?
You've done a lot of work.
- I know. - I was determined to work.
They said that they needed help, so I was going to work all day long.
You've done a lot of work.
It was hard for me to go to the kindergarten.
You preferred working.
- You preferred working. - Yes, I preferred working.
- I moved a lot of rocks, - Okay.
but it doesn't show.
This is outstanding work.
It has become prettier.
- Yes, it has. - The field has become bigger.
(Before restoration)
(After restoration)
It couldn't have been easy.
You did well.
- I'll come back to move rocks. - Please come again.
- Thank you for your hard work. - Call me tomorrow.
Take care. Let's meet again.
(They come back to Alkong and Dalkong's kindergarten.)
(Opening)
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Yes? - Alkong and Dalkong's guardians...
are here.
- Okay. They're going downstairs. - Okay.
There they are.
My goodness.
- How cute! - My goodness.
There are no other beings like dogs.
- I'll take their backpacks. - My goodness.
- Thank you. - Gosh.
- Wait. - Gosh.
- Dogs are always happy to see you. - Right.
How cute! Did you have fun?
- Mom, give him to me. - Did you have fun?
Go to your brother.
- Go to your brother. - How cute.
- The leash. - My goodness.
Hold on to the leash.
- Well done. - What did they learn today?
- What did they learn? - Yes.
Today, they learned how to walk next to the teacher...
instead of outrunning the teacher.
They learned how to sit, lie down,
- Sit and lie down? - stand,
wait, and come when called.
Will they listen to our commands?
Of course.
- They learned how to wait here. - Really?
They learned the command here.
There you go.
- You can use the same commands. - Okay.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Let's go. - There you go.
Let's go.
- You're so cute. - The leash.
Thank you. Take care.
- Have a nice weekend. - Take care.
- Thank you for your hard work. - Take care.
(They get into the car with Alkong and Dalkong.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
They had a good time at the kindergarten.
Let's go.
They must be tired. They're sleeping.
(Dozing off in Kian84's arms)
They used to avoid me.
- Now, they're leaning on my arms. - Right.
- They don't bark at you anymore. - Yesterday,
they treated me like a thief.
(They treated me like a thief.)
They realized that you weren't a bad person.
(Let's be friends.)
Are you going home now?
No.
We're here.
You guys are coming with me.
The leash. Here.
I don't see them very often.
- Will you walk them? - I wanted to do something for them.
- While you were out with them? - Yes.
Mom, take this.
Walk with me.
(This is exciting!)
(Feeling excited, he tries to run on his hind legs.)
- Why is he running so much? - He is happy.
He has so much energy.
Is that a proper run?
He finally found a fellow runner.
- Proper Run Crew. - Proper Run Crew.
- He is good. - Proper Run Crew.
You're walking well with your big brother.
He keeps running.
Where are you going?
Go ahead. Go where you want to go.
(Kian84 runs with him.)
(Happy)
Dalkong, let's run as well.
You're running well.
That's good.
Aren't you happy to take a walk with your big brother?
(I want to run some more!)
Let's run with them.
- Let's run! - Come here!
Let's run!
(This time, they run together with Kian84.)
(Let's run.)
(The three siblings race freely across the field.)
They're running well.
All right.
(This is nice.)
How cute!
When you do that, the outfit...
- Hello. - Hello.
- What? - Hello.
- Did you book a photo session? - Hello.
Nice to meet you.
They're Alkong and Dalkong.
With the dog that passed away,
Candy,
we had a family portrait.
(We had a family portrait.)
We had it.
In retrospect,
only that photo remains.
It has been about four months...
since the dogs became a family.
I decided to get our photos taken at the canola flower field...
and went there.
Please stand close.
Gosh, there you go.
- You're doing a great job. - That's it.
How cute!
I'll take photos like this.
(It's okay.)
- How cute! - Look over here.
(Hold on.)
(Sniffing)
Is it the pollen?
Smile. In 1, 2, 3.
Smile like this.
- That's it. In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
Alkong and Dalkong, look here.
One more time. Stay still.
I have a pollen allergy.
- Really? - The canola flowers...
were killing me.
- Stay. - Stay.
- Stay. - I'll take a photo of this.
- Good. - Stay.
All right.
The real son is struggling a lot.
(His nose becomes very runny.)
Please look over here.
(Sneezing)
(He can't help but sneeze.)
All right.
That's...
(1 second before sneezing)
That's a good one.
They take amazing photos.
- I'm sorry. - You're struggling a lot.
- Shall I hold them? - Yes.
Where is your mom?
- Dalkong, stay. - Where is your mom?
Mom.
- Mom. - You look beautiful, Mom.
Please arrange your hair.
Alkong, look at Mom.
I wouldn't call myself a filial son.
There are many sons like me.
That isn't true.
I think they're about the same.
After Candy passed away,
the atmosphere was very depressed and quiet at home.
Those dogs bring energy into the house.
I'm thankful for them.
- Those are amazing photos. - How cute.
Mom said this.
"Hee Min, don't think that you're a good person..."
"for bringing stray dogs."
"We became happy..."
"because they chose us."
To be honest,
I thought it was my good deed.
- It's true. - I thought it was my good deed.
(Well...)
In any case, I think...
it's a win-win situation for us and the dogs.
Let's go.
- Well done. - Thank you.
- Thank you for your hard work. - Thank you.
- Thank you. Take care. - Alkong and Dalkong, stay healthy.
He wants Mom to hold him.
He loves Mom so much.
Let's go and get some medicine.
You need medicine.
We can go to the pharmacy.
- Let's hurry. - Mom! This way.
There's one over there.
(The Reliable Furry Siblings Next to the Awkward Good Son)
(I Live Alone)
- It's great to see you! - It's great to see you!
There's great news for our Rainbow Club.
At the Baeksang Arts Awards,
Kian84 won the Male Entertainer Award!
- Yes! - Yes!
Congratulations!
It was a vivid moment.
When he went up to receive the reward,
I felt emotional.
- Really? - I'm so happy for you.
- I watched it live. - Thank you.
I've learned so much from you.
- Thank you so much. - Congratulations once again.
Kian84 has...
written history in the variety show world.
- Right. - Right.
Just like Kian84 who has just received an award,
this person is really popular in variety shows these days.
The preview of him got so many views.
Please welcome Lee Seon Min!
(Lee Seon Min)
(What did your wife say?)
(I'm single.)
(The one who certainly looks like a married man)
(Views: 1.83 million, 1.59 million, and 1.22 million)
(He took over YouTube with his energy.)
(The comedian with 10 years of experience...)
(who is showing a great performance everywhere)
Right. Hello, everyone.
I've been living alone for 19 years.
I'm Comedian Lee Seon Min. Hello!
You're not older than me, right?
I was born in the Year of the Dragon.
- So that's 1976? - No.
- You were born in 1988? - Right.
I was born in 1988.
I'm the same age as G-DRAGON.
- G-DRAGON? - Right.
Right.
- It's my first time meeting him. - Right.
- But his eyes... - Right.
- The color of his eyes... - He looks like a foreigner.
- The color of his eyes is unique. - Right.
I have olive eyes.
- Right. - I've never seen that color before.
There's someone else who has similar eyes as me.
- Seo Kang Jun. - I see.
- Just the eyes are similar. - Right.
There's Go A Ra as well.
- Lee Sung Kyoung. - Just the eyes.
- Just the color of the eyes. - Right.
(Laughing)
He has lived alone for 19 years.
He's truly single. He has never gotten married.
- That's right. - Truly single?
He's truly single.
Let's dive into Lee Seon Min's life!
(The Single Man of Certainty)
(The room is dark because of the blackout curtains.)
- What is that? - What is that?
Isn't that a respirator?
That's a PAP machine.
People who have bad snoring or sleep apnea issues use that.
It continuously applies air pressure into the nose.
Right.
(He's sleeping with the PAP machine on.)
He looks like a man from the future.
Hello.
I've lived alone for 19 years. I'm Comedian Lee Seon Min.
It feels like he was married once.
That's what it feels like.
He's wearing such cute pajamas.
- He looks like a baby. - Right.
A very big baby.
(Crying)
(He does a stretch.)
(Getting up)
If I remember it correctly, I moved places ten times.
I believe this is my 11th house.
I moved to Seoul when I was 21.
I started living in a boarding house.
I've lived in a gosiwon and a studio apartment.
I've also lived in a rooftop house and a semi-basement house.
I've made it here after living in those places.
And as I've lived alone for 19 years,
I brought with me all of my belongings.
They're stuck in each corner of the house.
Right. You keep getting more things as you live alone.
- Right. - You keep getting more things.
Unnecessary things should be thrown out.
(In the middle of the spacious living room,)
(there are 2 large drying racks!)
The Christmas tree is still up.
Shouldn't this be thrown out?
That tree to me...
is like a veteran tree.
- A veteran tree? - Right.
- A veteran tree at home? - That tree feels like...
- it will protect me. - I see.
It brings a sense of comfort.
(Next to the living room with the veteran tree,)
(there's a kitchen with a lot of traces of life.)
There are a lot of things.
Right. They're still in place.
(There are many supplements that kept him healthy for 19 years.)
(The dressing room...)
(is filled with clothes beyond its limit.)
(There are many clothes in the bedroom as well.)
Why are there so many clothes?
It's just like my house.
- We're all the same. - We're all the same.
(Scratching)
(Rubbing)
(Sniffling)
(Gosh, I should get up.)
(He heads over to the kitchen after barely managing to get up.)
(Scratching)
(He drinks a cup of water on an empty stomach.)
(He opens the fridge after quenching his thirst.)
(The fridge is packed.)
- It's well-organized. - It looks well-organized.
(Thinking)
(He grabs something after thinking for a while.)
(Tossing)
(Did he take out leftover ingredients from the fridge?)
- He must be cooking. - He must be cooking.
(Taking out)
(He gets out the leftover meat as well.)
I don't throw out any of the ingredients I have.
- I see. You use them later. - Right.
(He checks the doenjang by smelling it.)
- You check by the smell. - Right.
I believe that pastes...
can be kept for a long time.
So I don't throw them out.
(After getting out the ingredients,)
(he grabs the rice bag.)
He's making rice.
(He measures it by eye.)
Gosh, he's making rice?
I make rice as well these days.
- Really? - Yes.
Isn't it too much work?
But doing that on my day off...
- gives me peace. - It must make you happy.
Making rice is a pleasant thing to do.
- It must be a hobby. - Right.
(Collecting)
(Dripping)
He just estimates it.
I always put my hand in...
- Same here. - and do what I learned to do.
(It will take 30 minutes to cook.)
(He grabs the frying pan and pot after preparing the rice.)
(He gets a good amount of water in the pot.)
(He throws in some kelp...)
(and frozen anchovies.)
- It's a broth. - You're making a broth?
I make a broth for any kind of jjigae.
Why don't you use the broth packs that are sold?
There are times when it contains ingredients I don't want.
- Right. - I see.
There are times when it contains dried shrimp.
Right. That is why I only use kelp and big anchovies.
- That's all that is needed. - I use just a lot of those.
The kelp and anchovies bought last for around two years.
- They last for a long time. - Broth packs can be used...
about ten times.
- Right. - Right.
There are some types of ramyeon that have kelp in them.
I add ten more pieces of kelp when I have those.
You add more.
- You like kelp? - I do.
I got kelp candy as a gift. I should've brought it.
- Kelp candy? - Right.
You can have all of it.
(It's okay. You can have all of it.)
- I don't need the candy. - He's so polite.
It doesn't sound pleasant.
(He grabs the cabbage while the broth boils.)
(He washes just what he needs.)
They're big pieces.
That's a man who lives alone.
Right.
(He takes out another bowl.)
(He throws in the meat into the bowl.)
In my 20s, I ate twice as much as I eat now.
When I bought ingredients back then,
there were barely any leftovers.
But as I eat less often at home now,
I end up throwing out a lot of the ingredients.
Whenever there are leftover ingredients,
I try to make something with them.
I try my best not to throw out ingredients.
(Seon Min is cooking with leftover ingredients again.)
(He washes the garlic that was left in the fridge.)
(He slices the garlic skillfully.)
(Taking out)
- Gosh! - A mortar?
It's been a while to see a mortar.
I saw those when I was in elementary school.
(He crushes the garlic right away.)
When I buy minced garlic,
- it changes in color over time. - Right.
It costs around 4 to 5 dollars.
This much garlic can be bought with that.
- Right. - Whole garlic cloves.
(He takes out the pepper from the cupboard.)
- He's really good. - Right. He makes it look easy.
The seasoning is done right away in the mortar.
(With the experience of living alone for 19 years,)
(he makes the sauce in a flash.)
(There we go.)
(The sauce is poured over the meat right away.)
- What is that? - Is it seasoned bulgogi?
- Spicy stir-fried pork? - It's spicy stir-fried pork.
- Spicy stir-fried pork. - Spicy stir-fried pork.
(The meat is marinated in the fridge for a while.)
It's better marinated even if it's for ten minutes.
(The mortar gets rinsed right away.)
(There are 16 minutes left until the rice is ready.)
(Picking out)
(The anchovy broth gets boiled in the meantime.)
He dropped a piece.
(Eating)
He doesn't disappoint.
(The dropped piece can be eaten.)
(Turning open)
(He adds a spoon of traditional doenjang to the broth.)
- It looks quite old. - I think it's traditional doenjang.
The doenjang is around eight years old.
Eight years?
(The sliced cabbage pieces get added as well.)
- Cabbage doenjang soup? - Right.
Cabbage doenjang soup.
It's my soul food...
from ever since I started living alone.
- It's the best. - It tastes great.
(He prepares the vegetables for the spicy stir-fried pork.)
- You buy unpeeled onions, right? - I buy unpeeled onions.
If you look down there, you'll find the onion net.
- The onion net? - Right.
(The cleanly washed onion gets sliced.)
(He slices the mushrooms as well.)
(He uses the knife without hesitation.)
Will we only have guests who are certain about what they're doing?
(Will we only have guests who are certain about what they're doing?)
(He opens the fridge again with certainty.)
- The meat? - The meat must be taken out.
(Stirring)
(The well-marinated meat gets thrown in.)
(Throwing in the vegetables)
(Seon Min's stove is very busy.)
(The man who has lived alone for 19 years looks relaxed.)
(It gets cooked nicely.)
It looks good.
It looks amazing.
The rice is ready.
(The rice gets ready right on time.)
(He prepares 2 dishes in 30 minutes.)
He's really quick.
- Gosh, I suddenly feel hungry. - He's a great cook.
Right.
(The doenjang soup gets poured into the bowl as well.)
(Has the rice cooked nicely?)
(Fluffy)
- It looks nice. - It looks nice.
The rice turned out well.
You did that as soon as you got up.
It's the most important routine in my day.
Is that so?
(Rushing over)
(Shall I start eating now?)
(The perfect homemade meal of the one who lived alone for 19 years)
- It's the perfect homemade meal. - It's perfect.
It's the perfect homemade meal.
(Grabbing the remote control)
UFC.
Hold on!
Wasn't that too scary?
He sounded like a retired fighter.
(He sounded like a retired fighter.)
"Are my juniors doing well?"
He sounded like a retired fighter who still wants to fight.
This was what he felt like to me.
He was like the main character of the movie, "Home Alone,"
and his mother never came back.
He was like Kevin who aged just like that.
How many years was his mother away...
- for him to be like that? - His mother never came back.
Kevin was left alone for around 40 years.
His mother didn't come back for 40 years?
(How long will I be home alone?)
(He starts by slurping the doenjang soup.)
(Satisfied)
(Sticking)
(He takes a bite right away.)
That looks great!
- That's the best! - He's making it look so good.
It looked like a tooth fell out.
- Gosh! - It was too hot.
(He takes another bite of the doenjang soup...)
(as if nothing happened.)
(This is it.)
(He uses the spoon to pick up the spicy stir-fried pork.)
- Right. You must use the spoon. - It's been a while to have that.
Men love spicy stir-fried pork.
(Munching)
(I can't miss out on the lettuce wraps.)
(A spoonful of rice,)
(ssamjang,)
(and a good amount of meat)
(A very good amount)
(Eating it in one bite)
- This is pleasant to watch. - Right.
I try to eat as much as I can on my days off.
To myself who feels exhausted from work,
(To myself who feels exhausted from work)
it's a ray of hope.
I must eat as heavily as I can.
How should I put it?
That's how it feels like a gift for myself.
It makes you feel like you're resting up.
Right.
(Scooping)
(Here's the gift for you, Seon Min.)
"Here's the gift for you."
(Feeling grateful)
(Slurping)
(He munches the food without stopping.)
- He eats really quickly. - Right.
(Quick...)
(and precise)
- He won't leave any food. Great. - Gosh.
It sounds great as well.
(I cannot leave a single grain of rice.)
So you finish everything you see.
- Right. - That's amazing.
(It's the same with the spicy stir-fried pork.)
(He drinks from the bowl while he's at it.)
(Clean)
- It's so clean. - Right.
- This is a great sight. - It's so clean.
- Right. - Seon Min,
did you eat the dried laver desiccant?
(Did you eat the dried laver desiccant?)
I took it out of my mouth...
after putting it in without realizing it.
Didn't you pour the silica gel over the spicy stir-fried pork?
(Didn't you pour the silica gel over the spicy stir-fried pork?)
I feel bad if I don't eat like that.
I can wash the dishes when I see the bottom.
(I must clean up now.)
(Opening)
The ssamjang is the only thing that's left.
(He takes out a plate...)
(and opens the fridge again?)
(The Korean melon appears for dessert.)
- They taste great these days. - Right.
I must have fruits that are in season.
(He takes out just what he needs.)
(He opens the freezer this time.)
Summer Crush.
It's taken out for it to melt a bit?
(Grabbing)
(He cuts the Korean melon with the kitchen knife.)
- He's good. - He's good.
With the kitchen knife.
(With his skillful hands,)
(he cuts it into two large pieces.)
(I must eat before I digest all the food.)
(Sitting)
(He sits in front of his meal buddy again.)
(Crunch)
(Satisfied)
It feels like I'm watching someone's father.
The father left alone at home after the mother goes on a trip.
It feels like a father left at home for a while.
Right. It's Kevin who has grown old.
Kevin is sticking out his belly like that?
His mother never came back.
Kevin has aged like that?
(CODE KUNST's opinion is quite logical.)
Why are his eyes so focused?
(After easily clearing the Korean melon,)
(he starts melting the ice cream.)
- Right. - It's nice to lower the fever.
I like taking it out at once.
- At once? - Without stopping.
It must be melted for a while to do that.
(Tearing)
(He takes it all out with all authority.)
- That moment feels great. - Right.
It must be melted from the outside to be able to do that.
(He devours it while watching TV.)
(Chewing)
(He eats it while watching mixed martial arts.)
(Fully focused)
Gosh!
What? All of a sudden?
(Throwing punches)
He must've watched highlights.
(He's shadow boxing all of a sudden?)
(He starts copying the moves out of nowhere.)
He must really like UFC.
I'm a big mixed martial arts fan.
I won't be getting into a fight in real life,
but in case I meet an assailant,
I put together combo moves.
You're going to do that in front of the assailant?
(Throwing punches)
I have a few moves of my own.
(I have everything planned.)
(Picking up)
(He eats his ice cream while putting together combo moves.)
(Sucking)
(He sucks it until the very last drop.)
So you finish that until the last drop as well.
It's all about the last drop.
- You end up eating the wrapper. - Right.
Even the ice cream on the wrapper tastes good.
Right.
We're all the same.
- We're all the same. - Right.
(He puts the wrapper in the trash can.)
(The used dishes are put in the sink.)
(He does the dishes right away.)
(Scrubbing until they are squeaky clean)
(Jabbing)
Shadowboxing is part of his daily routine.
(He jabs once in a while too.)
- He's well-built. - He has the solidest build.
I know. He's built like a tank.
You can break an apple with your hand, right?
But my hands are small,
- which is a twist. - Oh, your hands are small.
- My hands are tiny. - They're quite cute.
- Oh, my. They're really small. - They really are small.
(Surprised)
- Why? You think you can beat me? - I think...
That suddenly crossed my mind.
CODE KUNST, you can't!
He's thinking of the combo attacks right now.
You've already been hit seven times in my head.
(You've already been hit 7 times in my head.)
Already?
(Knocked out from 7 combo attacks)
He's already been hit.
He's already been knocked out.
(After cleaning up flawlessly,)
(he goes to the bathroom to wash his face.)
(He quickly finished washing his face.)
(Flopping down)
(Grabbing lotion)
(Squeezing out)
- Goodness. - Squeezing.
He's really frugal.
You need to squeeze out even the last drop.
(Slathering all over the face)
- There's a pleasure it gives. - That's right.
(Let it soak in.)
(After a super fast skincare routine)
(Thinking)
(What should I wear?)
(Wandering around, looking for clothes)
- His belly is... My gosh. - My gosh.
(Taking it off)
His belly is...
(Putting it down)
(Picking up clothes from the drying rack)
(He quickly gets changed.)
(Grabbing a pair of cotton work gloves as well)
- Work gloves? - Work gloves?
I use them often too.
Doesn't it look like he'll go to the mountains?
His outfit shouts running for sure.
(All set for going out)
(Shall I go out now?)
What will he do? I can't wait to see.
Gosh, the weather is great.
(The sunlight is amazing.)
(Heading somewhere while enjoying the sunlight)
(Glancing)
(Rummaging through)
Gosh, how pretty.
(Taking a photo)
The flowers these days are really pretty.
(Adding a heart as well)
You're not sending it to your wife, are you?
- I don't have a wife. - Oh, right.
It's for his daughter.
- Daughter? - His daughter.
Okay.
(He walks on after taking satisfying selfies.)
What is it?
(To be continued)
This is nice.
(Soon, a hiking trail appears.)
(Seon Min came outside.)
What is it?
This is nice.
(Soon, a hiking trail appears.)
It takes less than 30 seconds until I get to the hiking trail.
- It's so close! - That's the best.
It was one of the biggest reasons I moved there.
(Trudging)
(While walking along the trail,)
(Seon Min walks into a building.)
(A mountain gym inside the building)
- It's a mountain gym. - Oh, it's a mountain gym.
(Traces of the masters who know good value for money)
- A gym like that in the mountains? - It's well-equipped.
Gyms like that are well-managed these days.
(The equipment is well-managed.)
- Look. They're masters. - The masters.
There are a lot of elderly people.
That's right.
It's the mountain gym in Mount Yongwang.
It's where I go at least once a week.
The ages of people who go there vary from...
- teens to those in their 80s. - Right. There are teens these days.
When I go there,
I'm on the younger side. When I see the seniors...
in their 70s or 80s working out there,
I get motivated.
I also think I shouldn't fall behind.
It's where my passion to work out ignites.
It's where you reflect on yourself.
(Young man Seon Min has come for a cost-effective workout.)
(Looking around)
Hello.
It's so nice...
- that it's close to your place. - It is really nice.
(Scanning the masters)
(Taking them out)
(Putting on the precious work gloves he brought from home)
- Oh, the work gloves. - That's why he brought them.
The work gloves.
(He also prepared cost-effective workout equipment.)
(Starting lightly at first)
Starting lightly with 20kg.
I don't really lift heavy weights.
I do it lightly.
(Exhaling)
(Exhaling sharply)
(Groaning)
(He lightly finished warming up.)
(Breathing out)
Why do you breathe out so much?
It's my workout routine.
When you breathe out...
(Exhaling)
- He's like... - It's a cardio.
Come on!
You move your shoulders more.
- What is that? - I learned to work out like that.
Because of that sound, he looks like he's good at it.
Right.
(Pretending to be a master with a sound effect)
(Adding more weight as a master should)
Gosh, it's clean.
The equipment in a mountain gym used to be rusty.
But they got better these days.
So many people go there these days,
- They are rubber weight plates. - so there's no space.
(Taking it off)
- Oh, no. - Gosh.
You should always be careful of that.
Because my upper body is long, I often bump into it.
(Glancing)
(He gets back to his senses and focuses on the workout.)
(Repeating it easily)
- It's 60kg. - That's good.
It's not easy to lift 60kg.
(Exhaling)
You do make a lot of noise.
(Wrapping up with a weird sound)
(Getting up)
(Scanning the masters while breathing heavily)
(Working out hard)
That's...
- I learn new techniques a lot. - I mean...
What was that? Was he working out his back?
He was working out his arms, then did the back.
You can't tell which part of the body they work out.
- They all have their methods. - Yes, it is a type of workout.
(The masters are quietly training.)
(Looking around cautiously)
(I can't just rest.)
(Young man Seon Min pushes himself more.)
He added more weight.
(Exhaling)
Don't people stare at you...
when you make loud exhales like that at the mountain gym?
There are some seniors who scold me from time to time.
"Be quiet!"
"What do you think you're doing?"
They'd go like that.
- "Be quiet!" - They have strong discipline.
I see. They're strict.
(Seon Min became less disciplined.)
It's like "The Flying Superboard."
(Working out his legs while making loud noises)
(Grunting)
(Groaning)
(Gosh!)
(Grunting)
Be quiet!
(Channeling a senior)
- I'm sorry. - Please be quiet!
- I'm sorry. - You're not the only one here.
(Elderly Moo exploded as Seon Min was too loud.)
You can't help but make noises...
- when you work out your legs. - That's true,
but you deserved to be scolded.
You're right.
(Seon Min works out especially noisily.)
(Making so much fuss)
(He may be loud, but he works out hard.)
- He's working out hard. - Right.
(Panting)
(Flexing)
Gosh, look at his legs.
- That's amazing. - He looks like a ssireum wrestler.
Why are you doing that?
I was flexing them to see how well it hit my muscles.
That happens. When you work out,
- you want to try doing that. - That's right.
It's only natural to react like that because it's the mountain gym.
I wouldn't have been able to do that at an indoor gym.
That's why you go to a mountain gym.
That's right.
(Shall I get up?)
(Staggering)
(Moving to a different spot while staggering)
(Thump)
(Staring)
Wait. It's a young man.
He was still in school.
(Staring intently)
Being territorial a little.
He's being territorial.
You got it.
Let's do it.
Why would you cheer him on all of a sudden?
I'm establishing hierarchy.
- "I'm stronger than you." - You can do it.
- That's it. - You don't know him, do you?
- No, he was a stranger. - He was?
(Approaching)
Why would you approach him?
You were going to help, but he was done.
He was done before you could help.
- How many did you do? - I did around 30.
- You can do it. - Okay.
What's your body goal?
I want to become like Arnold Schwarzenegger.
(Movie star Arnold Schwarzenegger)
What... What did you say?
Arnold... Did I hear that right?
- Arnold Schwarzenegger. - Yes.
- From "Robocop?" - Yes.
(It's "Terminator.")
- Okay. - "Robocop?"
- You can do it. - Okay!
Try lifting.
Let's start becoming Arnold Schwarzenegger from the beginning.
Arnold Schwarzenegger also started with pink dumbbells.
- You get what I mean, right? - Yes.
How many of this can you do?
Well... Twenty?
Go. Let's go.
Two. Three.
- Training him all of a sudden? - Four.
Six. Wait, you're good.
(The aspiring Arnold Schwarzenegger gets motivated by his praise.)
- Ten. Eleven. - That's good.
Do nine more.
You can lift them. Two.
- Three. - You can do it.
- That's good. - Four.
You can lift them. Two.
(Shaking)
- Help... Lift them for him. - Three.
- You should... That's it. - Hold them for him.
Six. Go.
(I'll help you.)
Seven.
Eight.
(Lifting with all his might)
- Nine. - Overcome it. You can do it!
One more. The last one.
Nine.
Arnold Schwarzenegger!
That's it!
(He finished the 1st set successfully.)
(Moved)
- That's so sudden. - So suddenly?
They sweated a lot.
You can do it. Anyone can fail.
- Just do better next time. Got it? - Okay.
That was great. Good.
That's it for me. I'm leaving.
Let's say hi if we see each other next time.
I'm leaving. You can do it.
- What? - What? You're leaving like that?
(He quickly packed his stuff.)
- You got it! - Okay.
- What's with that old man? - Who's he?
That's brave of him, though.
- Seriously. - To do that at the mountain gym.
I was so proud of him.
I feel like he'd become someone, though.
(He goes somewhere without taking a break.)
(Fully enjoying the phytoncide in the mountain)
(Breathing out)
Gosh, this is nice.
Lying around at home is surely nice,
but when the sunlight is nice, I'd sleep an hour or two less...
even though it's tiring.
I must go out and get moving while getting the sunlight...
to recharge my energy.
I think that's my driving force.
That's how I'm like too.
(Climbing down the mountain after recharging)
You feel rather better...
- if you go out. - That's true.
(After hiking, he diligently heads somewhere.)
- He's not going home. - He's going somewhere.
My gosh!
(After hiking, he diligently heads somewhere.)
(Clunk)
- Wait! Timeout! - Oh, my.
I only grabbed it lightly to stretch my shoulders.
- But it... - Just how strong are you?
No, it was loose.
- I mean... This is... - That's...
He's like the Hulk.
- It was a first for me too. - He's incredibly strong.
(Quickly fixing it)
(Dumbfounded)
(Did something happen?)
I reported it to the district office,
- Well done. - and they took care of it.
(He quickly flees the scene.)
(A subway station?)
(Where did he go after coming down to a subway station?)
(Striding effortlessly as he's familiar with the place)
It's the nation's beloved store.
I just stop by the store on purpose on the way home...
even though there's nothing I want to buy.
But I always end up with something in my hands when I leave.
You can never leave the store empty-handed.
I came to live in Seoul after retaking the CSAT.
It cost a lot to live alone in the city.
My parents paid my tuition,
so I tried to earn my own allowances.
I naturally developed a habit of being budget-conscious.
- That's true. - That's true.
Around 80 percent of household goods is from that store.
(Thinking)
(Staring intently)
It's 2 dollars for 6.
It's a good store for items like that.
One dollar for three. One dollar for four.
One dollar for four.
Then...
(He picked a set of 4 he could get at 1 dollar.)
(Super focused)
Seventy...
(It's 1 dollar for 70.)
(1 dollar for 50)
(He picked a set of 70 he could get at 1 dollar.)
All flosses are similar.
So I got one with a higher quantity.
(I see.)
(He compares each dish sponge.)
He's really careful.
(He picked one that costs 1 dollar.)
There are many excellent items that cost one dollar.
If it's above three dollars, it's no longer an option.
If it's 2 dollars, I'd wonder why it's 2 dollars.
I'd compare it to the one-dollar item similar to it.
If it's not worth spending twice as much, I'd get the one-dollar one.
I calculate fast. I'd compare them,
and if there's a reason it costs three dollars, then I'd get it.
Otherwise, I get the one-dollar item.
I can relate to that.
(Calculating the cost-effectiveness in his head)
(Looking around in search of cost-effective items)
What is it?
A decorating item.
(Evaluating cost-effectiveness)
(Grabbing)
You have a few of them at home.
- I have about two at home. - Right?
(A little treat while shopping on a budget)
Owls are considered symbols of wealth.
After I brought that home,
things started working out for me.
So I got another owl.
That's luxury to me.
(Holding the luxury owl tightly,)
(he heads to check out.)
(Happiness of 10.5 dollars including the luxury owl)
He grabbed a lot of items,
- but it only cost 10.5 dollars? - It's the best.
Happiness of 10 dollars in 2026?
(Putting them in his backpack 1 by 1)
(That was incredible shopping.)
(His steps are light as he shopped smart.)
Hello.
Welcome.
(Seon Min heads somewhere.)
A fruit store?
Is it a market?
It's a store I go to as often as Daiso.
(Fresh and...)
(cheap)
(Seon Min's favorite vegetable store)
- It's cheap. My goodness. - It's cheap.
Vegetables are much cheaper at a market like that.
I buy vegetables there, no matter what.
(Staring)
(Let's see.)
(Scanning carefully for plump garlic)
(He's done picking garlic.)
(On top of garlic and chili, he gets Karahyang mandarins too.)
I'll take these.
It's 7.5 dollars.
(Total: 7.5 dollars)
That's only 7.5 dollars?
That's cheap.
- Thank you. - Have a good day.
(Trudging after getting vegetables)
(He comes back home after a successful grocery run.)
(Exhausted)
(Putting away the vegetables as soon as he gets home)
(Piling 1 by 1)
(Gulping down)
(Dripping)
(Coughing)
That happens.
(Choking up on water)
Why are you so impatient?
He has the energy of a dad when he's single.
- I know. - Yes.
(Coughing)
Goodness.
(Coughing again for the 2nd time)
(It's time to wash off the sweat.)
(Wiping)
(Pressing hard)
(The lotion he barely managed to squeeze out in the morning)
(He's struggling with lotion again.)
Will any of it come out?
(It looks like he'll squeeze out what's not even there.)
I feel like the plastic will melt out instead of the lotion.
(Grunting)
(A tiny amount)
A bit of it came out.
(He uses even the last drop of it.)
(Opening)
(He washes the clothes he wore that day.)
(Where did it go?)
(Taking)
- Shampoo? - You use shampoo for it?
You use that?
I have a lot of leftover shampoo.
I have hair loss,
so I get a lot of hair loss shampoo as a gift.
But it's a waste to throw out the ones that expired.
So I use them as a detergent.
But...
Is it okay to use that?
I used it to wash clothes a lot in the military, though.
- Yes. - That's right.
- It's non-toxic. - It has strong cleansing power.
I see.
I feel like Seon Min is the perfect ambassador for Greenpeace.
- Greenpeace. - Greenpeace. He protects the Earth.
I do believe I should be mindful first.
- That's right. - Be mindful first?
- I have that belief. - You're the one...
- Of course. - who loves nature.
- "I should save things first." - Yes.
(He diligently folds the remaining laundry as well.)
(Opening the shelf...)
He's good at organizing.
(and putting the towels in)
- Good. - That makes me feel good.
(Putting away other clothes 1 by 1)
- He's good at basic organization. - Yes.
- I know. - He just has a lot of stuff.
- That's right. - He's well-organized.
Right, I am.
(All done.)
(Throwing)
(Goodness)
(Grunting)
He finally lay down.
- That must feel refreshing. - How nice.
That's when it's most relaxing.
(Dropping)
(Moving up and down)
- There's a magnet on his belly. - It's...
Are you charging the phone wirelessly?
Charging wirelessly?
There's a magnet on his belly.
He's taking a nap.
(Charging the phone with his belly)
That's when napping feels the best.
- Right. You feel drowsy. - You can sleep soundly.
(I should get up, though.)
(Heading to the kitchen, resisting the temptation to take a nap)
It's time for lunch.
(He's so busy.)
(Rustling)
(He took out a whole chicken from the fridge?)
(Taking it out)
It's a dish I make often.
(What is it?)
(Putting it in cold water first)
(Tapping in)
- Is it one-pot chicken? - What is it?
(A bag of garlic he tore open on the side)
Garlic.
Washing them in the bag? Nice.
- That's smart. - I do that too.
- That way, you use less water. - That's right.
(Dripping)
He poured them out. Is he adding them all?
- Will he add them all? - He must be.
It's the food I eat when I'm low on energy.
"All this garlic will go into my stomach."
It's ginseng chicken soup loaded with garlic.
(Seon Min's special dish)
Yes, you must have ginseng chicken soup.
(The soup starts to boil.)
(Since it's been boiled, he turns off the gas.)
There are impurities.
- I boil it once to filter them. - That's right.
(Amazed)
(A bag of herbal medicine that'll boost his energy)
(Adding lots of garlic, which is Seon Min's favorite)
It's somewhat relaxing.
(As he's skilled)
(Putting them deep into the hot water)
(Okay, it's all done.)
Watching him cook gives me the courage to try myself.
That's right.
Come over. I'll cook for you.
- Really? - Really?
I'll bring over spring water from the mountain nearby house.
- That'd be really nice. - It's better...
if you cook with spring water.
(Yes! I'll make sure to go over to your place.)
Okay.
(Wrapping it up with pepper)
Please be cooked fast.
(He just needs to boil it now.)
I don't think I'm lonely.
Surprisingly, this house is like paradise for me.
I'm taking this house as a foundation to work hard,
take good care of my health,
and give a reward to my body from time to time.
By collecting good energy,
I want to become a comedian who gives great laughs.
That's my goal.
(Blowing)
(Amazed)
- Bravo! - The scent of garlic...
and herbal medicine.
That's all you need.
(A perfect day that relieved built-up fatigue)
(Seon Min is Almost Unstoppable)
- Thank you for the clip. - Thank you.
- I was really happy watching it. - I was happy.
- Right. - Yes.
He's one of the comedians I almost always watch before I sleep.
I leave his video on because I like the lively energy...
he gives off.
And I'm not very active at home.
I want to try the food he makes.
(He wants to try the food Seon Min makes.)
He's the most solid among the people of my age...
that I know of.
- Thank you. - I'm happy.
Watching you made us happy...
even though you didn't do anything special.
Now I know why Seon Min is so widely loved.
He's the real deal.
- He doesn't exaggerate. - Right, he doesn't!
His daily life we saw today...
- wasn't exaggerated too. - That's right.
I think that's his charm.
I hope we get to see you often.
- Please come again. - I hope so too. Thank you.
- Thank you! - Thank you!
(We root for Seon Min's future endeavors.)
(Next story)
(The cute scene-stealer from "Undercover Miss Hong...")
(that drew everyone's attention)
(She was even nominated at the Baeksang Arts Awards.)
(The rookie actor who burst onto the scene)
(It's been 3 years since she started living alone.)
(Actress Choi Ji Su)
(Her small and precious roommate)
(Gamja)
(Welcome to Ji Su's house where Gamja lives too.)
(You can tell how skilled she is from every corner of her house.)
(She keeps her stuff thoroughly.)
(Solemnly with gloves on)
(A ritual she has to do every week)
(Cleaning like crazy)
(Cleaning...)
(gives her a dopamine boost.)
(Bathrooms show how you live.)
(Since it's my life, I'll clean every nook and cranny...)
(so it shines.)
(Shining)
(She becomes happier if she cleans this hard.)
(The dopamine boost party does not stop.)
(Switching...)
(the tools)
(Getting a full dopamine boost after switching the tools)
(She even explodes...)
(with cleaning the washing machine.)
(It's thrilling.)
(I Cleaned Thoroughly Again Today)
(Here's another man who is cleaning his house.)
All right.
(A refreshing day...)
(for a new beginning)
(His new family,)
(a new mattress)
- I don't think it'll work. - No?
(No?)
(Feeling especially upset today for having no elevator)
(I'm sorry about this.)
(You can just push it.)
(I'm pushing.)
(Struggling)
(Ringing)
(No! I didn't mean to press the doorbell.)
(Oh, no. It came off.)
(Am I dreaming?)
(Soaked in sweat)
(I must see it through. I'll freshen up the balcony too.)
(Putting on the scrubber)
(Splashing)
(Oh, my. This feels so clean.)
(Goodbye, deep-seated grime!)
(Refresh Day)